var questions = {
    category: {
        animals: {
            q1: {
                question: "Which of these dinosaurs lived during the Jurassic Period?",
                answers: {
                a: "Triceratops",
                b: "Stegosaurus",
                c: "Eoraptor",
                d: "Tyrannosaurus Rex",
                },
                correct: "b"
            },
            q2: {
                question: "Which of the following is NOT a characteristic of reptiles?",
                answers: {
                a: "They are warmblooded",
                b: "Most lay eggs",
                c: "They have thick scaly skin",
                d: "They breathe with lungs",
                },
                correct: "a"
            },
            q3: {
                question: "Which of these mammals lay eggs?",
                answers: {
                a: "Echidna",
                b: "Bongo",
                c: "Kiwi",
                d: "Southern right whale",
                },
                correct: "a"
            },
            q4: {
                question: "What is the term for a young horse?",
                answers: {
                a: "Cub",
                b: "Cygnet",
                c: "Foal",
                d: "Calf",
                },
                correct: "c"
            },
            q4: {
                question: "What is the fastest animal on Earth?",
                answers: {
                a: "Cheetah",
                b: "Peregrine Falcon",
                c: "Leopard",
                d: "Hyena",
                },
                correct: "b"
            },
            q5: {
                question: "Which of these animals is NOT endangered?",
                answers: {
                a: "Red wolf",
                b: "Sperm Whale",
                c: "Capybara",
                d: "Jaguar",
                },
                correct: "c"
            },
            q6: {
                question: "Which animal could not survive in Africa?",
                answers: {
                a: "Hippopotamus",
                b: "Tsetse fly",
                c: "Wildcat",
                d: "Giraffe",
                },
                correct: "c"
            },
            q7: {
                question: "What is the most poisonous snake on the planet?",
                answers: {
                a: "Cobra",
                b: "Inland Taipan",
                c: "Western diamondback Rattlesnake",
                d: "Black mamba",
                },
                correct: "b"
            },
            q8: {
                question: "Which is the biggest species of shark?",
                answers: {
                a: "Great White shark",
                b: "Hammerhead shark",
                c: "Whale shark",
                d: "Basking shark",
                },
                correct: "c"
            },
            q9: {
                question: "What is a distinguishing feature of a marsupial?",
                answers: {
                a: "They change color to blend in with their environment",
                b: "They live most of their lives in trees",
                c: "They have very long necks",
                d: "They carry their young in an external pouch",
                },
                correct: "d"
            },
        },
        geography: {

        },
        movies: {
            q1: {
                question: "What was the top-grossing film for 2002?",
                answers: {
                a: "Signs",
                b: "Star Wars: Episode II",
                c: "My Big Fat Greek Wedding",
                d: "Spiderman",
                },
                correct: "d"
            },
            q2: {
                question: "Which 2005 film's tagline is \"Better Late Than Never\"?",
                answers: {
                a: "Fantastic Four",
                b: "The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy",
                c: "The Ring Two",
                d: "The 40 Year Old Virgin",
                },
                correct: "d"
            },
        },
        music: {

        },
        sports: {

        }
    }
}


/*
//////////////////////////////////////////////////
FORMAT FOR ADDING QUESTIONS:

var questions = {
    category: {
        animals: {
            q#: {
                question: <YOUR QUESTION HERE>,
                answers: {
                    a: <answer A>,
                    b: <answer B>,
                    c: <answer C>,
                    d: <answer D>,
                },
                correct: <THE CORRECT ANSWER LETTER>
                }
            }
        }
    }
}
//////////////////////////////////////////////////
*/